這不是行情分析。
This video is not market analysis.
這不是投資建議。
It is not investment advice.
這也不是叫你買任何代幣。
And it is not telling you to buy any token.
這是一個宇宙誕生的紀錄。
This is a record of the birth of a universe.
在《花果山台灣・K線西遊記》的世界裡，我們一直把市場形容為一個有引力的宇宙。
In the world of Flower Fruit Mountain Taiwan, K-Line Odyssey, we have always described the market as a universe governed by gravity.
而今天，這個宇宙第一次在鏈上留下了痕跡。
And today, this universe has left its first trace on the blockchain.
在這個系統裡，我們定義了一條最簡單、也最殘酷的法則。
In this system, we define a simple but brutal law.
沒有質量，就沒有位置。
No mass, no position.
KGEN 不是遊戲幣，也不是短線炒作的工具。
KGEN is not a game token. It is not a tool for short-term speculation.
它只代表一件事：存在的質量。
It represents one thing only: the mass of existence.
你持有多少，不是炫耀，而是你在這個宇宙裡站的位置。
How much you hold is not a symbol of pride, but a statement of where you stand in this universe.
這個宇宙沒有拉盤指令，也沒有暴富承諾。
There are no pump commands and no promises of instant wealth.
所有規則寫在鏈上，所有紀錄公開可查。
All rules are written on-chain. All records are publicly verifiable.
能量來自行為，位置來自結果。
Energy is created by action. Position changes through consequence.
這不是娛樂遊戲，而是一套長期存活的篩選系統。
This is not entertainment. It is a system designed for long-term survival.
今天你看到的不是終點，而是創世的第一天。
What you see today is not the end. It is only the first day of creation.
PrimeForge 以母機之名，開啟金融生命。
PrimeForge, in the name of the Mother Machine, initiates financial life.
花果山台灣・信念不滅・市場無界。
Flower Fruit Mountain Taiwan. Faith unbroken. Markets without boundaries.
市場成為神話。
Where the Market Becomes the Myth.
—— 樂天帝
— Rakuten Emperor.